The hunter becomes the hunted
Blood and Money is a thriller, crime, drama film directed by John Barr.
A retired veteran hunting in the Allagash backcountry of Maine
discovers a dead woman with a duffle bag full of money.
He soon finds himself in a web of deceit and murder.
Jim Reed, played by Tom Berenger.
Debbie, played by Kristen Hager.
Bill, played by Paul Ben-Victor.
Ray, played by Mark Sivertsen.
Jane, played by Erica McDermott.
Night Guard, played by Bates Wilder.
Blood and Money (formerly titled Allagash) is a 2020 American thriller
film directed by John Barr and starring Tom Berenger.
It is Barr's feature directorial debut.
The film explores themes of wilderness, maine, snow, deer hunting.
The tone is emotional and intense.